Prints and Printing Lantern Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- Prints (Box 1)
  - Sweden (Box 37)
    - Zorn, Anders L., 1860-1920 (Box 37)
  - Switzerland (Box 37)
    - Giacometti, Alberto, 1901- (Box 37)
    - Klee, Paul, 1879-1940 (Box 37)
    - Vallotton, Felix, 1865-1925 (Box 37)
  - Latin America (Box 37)
    - Cuba (Box 37)
    - Mexico (Box 37)
      - Various Artists (Box 37)
      - Charlot, Jean, 1891- (Box 37)
      - Mendez, Leopoldo, 1903-1934 (Box 37)
      - Moreno, Juan Jose (Box 37)
      - Orozco, Jose (Box 37)
      - Posada, Jose Guadalupe., 1851-1913 (Box 37)
      - Rivera, Diego (Box 37)
      - Sequeiros, David (Box 37)
  - United States (Box 38)
    - General (Box 38)
      - Land Battles (Box 38)
      - Naval Battles (Box 38)
    - Artists (Box 38)
      - Aitken, Robert (Box 38)
      - Anderson, Alexander (Box 38)
      - Arms, John Taylor (Box 38)
      - Audobon, John James, 1785-1874 (Box 38)
      - Bacher, Otto (Box 38)
      - Bacon, Peggy (Box 38)
      - Baker, John (Box 38)
      - Bassett, W.H. (Box 38)
      - Bell, E. (Box 38)
      - Bellows, George, 1882-1925 (Box 38)
      - Bennett, William, 1777-1844 (Box 38)
      - Bingham, Dodd & Co. (Box 38)
      - Birmelin, Robert (Box 38)
      - Bowen, Abel (Box 38)
      - Bowen, JT (Box 39)
      - Brandi, Mariano (Box 39)
      - Britton, Rey & Co. (Box 39)
      - Bufford, JHW, 1858-1872 (Box 39)
      - Burgis, William, act.c.1715-1731 (Box 39)
      - Burtler, Andrew R. (Box 39)
      - Cameron, J. (Box 39)
      - Carroll, John (Box 39)
      - Cassatt, Mary, 1845-1926 (Box 39)
      - Catlin, George, 1796-1872 (Box 39)
      - Charberlain, Samuel, 1893- (Box 39)
      - Cole, Thimoty (Box 39)
      - Copley, John S., 1738-1815 (Box 39)
      - Currie (Box 39)
      - Currier & Ives, Currier, Nathaniel, 1813-1888 (Box 39)
        - Maurer, L (Box 39)
        - Severin, C. (Box 39)
      - Davies, Arthur, 1862-1928 (Box 39)
      - Dawkins, Henry, ac.1753-1786 (Box 40)
      - Diedrich, Hunt (Box 40)
      - Doolittle, Amos, 1754-1832 (Box 40)
      - Durand, Asher B., 1796-1886 (Box 40)
      - Durrie, G. (Box 40)
      - Duval, P.S. (Box 40)
      - Eby, Kerr (Box 40)
      - Edwin, David, 1776-1841 (Box 40)
      - Emmes, Thomas (Box 40)
      - Endicott & Co. (Box 40)
      - Foster, John, 1648-1681 (Box 40)
      - Gallard, J. (Box 40)
      - Ganso, Emile (Box 40)
      - Goldtwaite, Anne (Box 40)
      - Goodman & Piggot (Box 40)
      - Gorky, Achille (Box 40)
      - Graham, George, c.1797 (Box 40)
      - Greenwood, John, 1727-1792 (Box 40)
      - Hand Forth, Thomas (Box 40)
      - Hart, Charles (Box 40)
      - Hart, George O., 1868-1933 (Box 40)
      - Hartwell, Kenneth (Box 40)
      - Hassam, Childe, 1859-1935 (Box 40)
      - Hatch & Co. (Box 40)
      - Havell, Robert Jr., 1793-1878 (Box 40)
      - Heath, James (Box 40)
      - Heintzelman, Arthur (Box 40)
      - Hill, John, 1770-1850 (Box 40–41)
      - Homer, Winslow, 1836-1910 (Box 41)
      - Hoogland, William (Box 41)
      - Hubbard, William (Box 41)
      - Hudson, William, Jr. (Box 41)
      - Hunt, Samuel Valentine (Box 41)
      - Hurd, Nathaniel, 1729-1777 (Box 41)
      - Hutty, Alfred (Box 41)
      - Illment, Pillbrow (Box 41)
      - Imbert (Box 41)
      - Jennys, Richard, Jr. (Box 41)
      - Jocelyn, Simons, 1799-1875 (Box 41)
      - Johnston, Thomas, c.1708-1767 (Box 41)
      - Kearney, Francis (Box 41)
      - Kellogg, E.C. (Box 41)
      - Kent, Rockwell, 1882- (Box 41)
      - Kircass, W. (Box 41)
      - Lankes, J.J. (Box 41)
      - Lawson, Robert (Box 41)
      - Le Count, J.J. (Box 41)
      - Leich, Chester (Box 41)
      - Leonhardt & Son (Box 41)
      - Lewis, Martin (Box 41)
      - Linton, William, J. (Box 41)
      - Logan, Robert Fulton (Box 41)
      - Longacre, James B. (Box 41)
      - Marshall, William E. (Box 41)
      - Meyer, Henry (Box 41)
      - Moore (Box 42)
      - Morse, Nathaniel (Box 42)
      - Murray, George (Box 42)
      - Norman, John, c.1748-1817 (Box 42)
      - O'Key, Samuel, 1765-1780 (Box 42)
      - Orr, Louis (Box 42)
      - Partridge, Roi (Box 42)
      - Peale, Charles Wilson, 1741-1827 (Box 42)
      - Peale, Rembrandt, 1788-1860 (Box 42)
      - Pelham, Peter, c.1684-1751 (Box 42)
      - Pelton, O. (Box 42)
      - Pennell, Joseph, 1857-1926 (Box 42)
      - Pollak & Doty (Box 42)
      - Predergast, Maurice, 1859-1924 (Box 42)
      - Price, Chester B. (Box 42)
      - Pytlak, Leonard, 1910- (Box 42)
      - Rawdon, Ralph (Box 42)
      - Regnier (Box 42)
      - Revere, Paul, 1735-1818 (Box 42)
      - Robertson (Box 42)
      - Ronnebeck, Arnold (Box 42)
      - Rosemberg, Louis (Box 42)
      - Rukikac, Rudolph (Box 43)
      - St. Memin, CBJF de, 1770-1852 (Box 43)
      - Sargent, John Singer, 1856-1925 (Box 43)
      - Sarony & Major (Box 43)
      - Sartain, William (Box 43)
      - Savage, Edward, 1761-1817 (Box 43)
      - Schanker, Louis, 1903- (Box 43)
      - Schutz, Anton (Box 43)
      - Seymour, S. (Box 43)
      - Sinclair, T. (Box 43)
      - Sloan, John, 1871-1951 (Box 43)
      - Soyer, Raphael, 1899- (Box 43)
      - Stickley, Gustav (Box 43)
      - Strickland (Box 43)
      - Stuant, Gilbert (Box 43)
      - Tait, Arthur F. (Box 43)
      - Tanner, Benjamin, 1775-1845 (Box 43)
      - Taskey, Harry L., 1892-1958 (Box 43)
        - B&W Thayer Co. (Box 43)
      - Thiebout, C., 1773-1832 (Box 43)
      - Turner (Box 43)
      - Tuttle, Henry E., 1890- (Box 43–44)
      - Webster, Herman A. (Box 44)
      - Weir, J. Alden, 1852-1919 (Box 44)
      - Wermuller, Adolf (Box 44)
      - Whistler, James A.M., 1834-1903 [Boxes 44-46] (Box 44)
        - Early Illustrations (Box 44)
        - Cities (Box 44)
          - Amsterdam (Box 44)
          - Bourges (Box 44)
          - Brussels (Box 44)
          - Zaandam (Box 45)
          - Paris (Box 45)
          - Loches (Box 45)
          - London (Box 45)
        - Genre (Box 45)
        - Models (Box 45)
        - Portraits (Box 45)
        - Self-Portraits (Box 45)
        - Print Sets (Box 45)
          - Coast Survey, 1850 (Box 45)
          - French Set, 1858 (Box 45)
          - Thames set, 1859-1871 (Box 46)
          - Venetian set, 1880 (Box 46)
          - 26 Etchings set, 1886 (Box 46)
          - Vitre (Box 46)
      - Wilcox, Frank N. (Box 46)
      - Wild, J.C. (Box 46)
      - Wolf, Henry (Box 46)
      - Wright, Joseph (Box 46)
- Miscellaneous printing and typography samples (Box 47)
  - General (Box 47)
  - 15th century (Box 47)
  - 16th century (Box 47)
    - Garamond, Claude (Box 47)
  - 17th century (Box 48)
  - 18th century (Box 48)
  - 19th century (Box 48)
  - 20th century (Box 48)
    - Clarendon Press (Box 48)
    - Dwiggins (Box 48)
    - Goudy, Frederic (Box 48)
    - Grabhorn Press (Box 48)
    - Koch, Rudolf (Box 48)
    - Nonesuch Press (Box 49)
    - University Press (Box 49)
    - Bruce Rogers (Box 49)